Guide to the H.E Butti Bin Bishr Collection AD.MC.093
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Studio Portraits of UAE Officials
  - A portrait of H.H. Sheikh Sultan Bin Zayed Bin Khalifa Al Nahyan., Circa 1969-1970; AD_MC_093_ref31_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 5.5 x 4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Individual Portraits; Royalty; United Arab Emirates; Studio Photography; Political Leadership; Sultan bin Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1953-2019
  - A studio portrait of Sheikh Suhail Bin Mubarak Al Ketbi., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref31_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 5.5 x 4.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Sheikhs; United Arab Emirates
  - A studio portrait of a man that worked for H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan., 12 Jan 1968; AD_MC_093_ref31_000004_000001; Al-Nil (UAE); 1 Photographic Prints 4.4 x 7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Men; Individual Portraits; Officials; English Writing; United Arab Emirates
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Dr. Mohammed Saeed Al Badi in military uniform., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref31_000005_000001; Gulf Photographer, Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; 1 Photographic Prints 8.5 x 6.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Facial Hair; Hats; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Studio Photography; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Medals/Insignia
  - A studio portrait of H.E. Dr. Mohammed Saeed Al Badi., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref31_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.5 x 6.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Studio Photography; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Individual Portraits
  - A portrait of Mohammed Bin Saeed Al Farad in Dibba, Al-Fujairah., Circa 1960-1970; AD_MC_093_ref31_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.8 x 13.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Men; Individual Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Facial Hair; Fujairah, United Arab Emirates; Buildings
- Album of Assorted Images of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr
  - The front cover of an album of assorted images of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1950-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.7 x 25.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    United Arab Emirates; Paris, France; Unknown Locations; Cairo, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Color Photography
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the right) with an unidentified man and three members of the Abu Dhabi military., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref32_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.8 x 13.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Cameras; United Arab Emirates; Officials
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) with a group of men during a unification talk., Circa 1969-1971; AD_MC_093_ref32_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.8 x 13.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; United Arab Emirates; Gatherings; Politics; Government; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Microphones; Facial Hair
  - H.H. Sheikh Rashid Bin Saeed Al Maktoum (middle) and H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Rashid Bin Saeed (right of Sheikh Rashid) with a group of men on a tour., Circa 1955-1965; AD_MC_093_ref32_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 16.3 x 21 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Unknown Locations; Gatherings; Royalty; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Political Leadership; Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1912-1990
  - From the left: a group portrait of Sheikh Maktoum Hasher Maktoum Al Maktoum, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and Sheikh Ahmed Bin Saeed Al Maktoum., Circa 1963-1964; AD_MC_093_ref32_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.5 x 10.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Officials; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Group Portraits; Political Leadership
  - An aerial view of Jamal Abdel Nasser Square in Dubai., Circa 1960-1965; AD_MC_093_ref32_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9.1 x 13.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Architecture; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Street Lamps; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Mosques; Religious Sites; Shops; Signs/Signposts
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle) reaching his hand towards another man in the desert., Circa 1958-1965; AD_MC_093_ref32_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 6.1 x 6.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Mountains/Hills; United Arab Emirates; Officials; Deserts
  - Front row, from the left: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, and H.E. Saeed Al Darmaki with a group of men behind them, including H.H. Sheikh Rashid Bin Saeed (behind Sheikh Zayed) at the Al Ain Palace Hotel., Circa 1969-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000008_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 17.6 x 12.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Signs/Signposts; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Hotels; Flags; Gatherings; Men; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr driving a car with three people in the passenger seat in Dubai., Circa 1956-1960; AD_MC_093_ref32_000009_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.8 x 13.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Streets/Roads; Clocks/Watches; Facial Hair; Children; Boys; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Officials
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr leaning on a truck., Circa 1956-1960; AD_MC_093_ref32_000010_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 6.1 x 6.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Officials; Men; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Unknown Locations
  - A portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr in a wooded area., Circa 1956-1960; AD_MC_093_ref32_000011_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 6.1 x 6.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Officials; Forest/Woodlands; Unknown Locations
  - Mohammed Al Ameri holding a shotgun outside of an arish hut near the Clocktower Roundabout in Dubai., 1957; AD_MC_093_ref32_000012_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 6.1 x 6.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Guns; Weapons; Individual Portraits; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Hunting; Birds; Animals
  - A group of people inside a cafeteria in Dubai., Circa 1945-1955; AD_MC_093_ref32_000013_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 6.1 x 6.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Restaurants/bars; Signs/Signposts; Streets/Roads; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Arabic Writing; Boys; Children
  - Sheikh Maktoum Hasher Maktoum Al Maktoum(left) sitting with an unidentified man., Circa 1960-1965; AD_MC_093_ref32_000014_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.5 x 10.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Sheikhs; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Clocks/Watches
  - A portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr during a trip to Paris with members of the Emirati delegation in the background., Circa 1969; AD_MC_093_ref32_000015_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Officials; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Paris, France; Individual Portraits; Streets/Roads; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Cars/Trucks; Transportation
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) sitting on sofas with two unidentified men., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref32_000016_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 10.5 x 15 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Unknown Locations; Officials; Furnishings
  - A view of the Eiffel Tower., Circa 1969; AD_MC_093_ref32_000017_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Eiffel Tower; Streets/Roads; Paris, France; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Street Lamps; Buildings; Architecture
  - A portrait of H.H. Sheikh Mubarak Bin Qarran Al Mansoori in a garden in Paris., Circa 1969; AD_MC_093_ref32_000018_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Individual Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Gardens; Officials; Paris, France; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Political Leadership
  - A studio portrait of Sheikh Hasher bin Maktoum Al Maktoum., Circa 1960-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000019_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12 x 8.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Sheikhs; Officials; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Studio Photography; United Arab Emirates
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr performing the Al Ayala dance with a crowd of men behind him., Circa 1965-1969; AD_MC_093_ref32_000020_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 14 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Crowds; Dancing; Swords/Knives; Weapons; Gatherings; United Arab Emirates; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Officials
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) with Ibrahim Bin Mohammed Al Hadidi Al Shamsi, Director of Foreign and Cultural Affairs, at the Diwan in Abu Dhabi., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref32_000021_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 10.5 x 7.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Carpets/Rugs; Offices
  - H.H. Sheikh Ahmad Bin Ali Al Thani and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (right) with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (background) upon Sheikh Ahmed's arrival to Abu Dhabi., Circa 1969-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000022_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 7.3 x 10.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Streets/Roads; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Clocks/Watches; Political Leadership; Sheikh, Ahmad bin Ali bin Abdullah bin Jassim bin Mohammed Al Thani, 1922-1977; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - A portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr reading a book., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref32_000023_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 8.5 x 10.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Books; Officials; United Arab Emirates
  - A group portrait of officials congregating at the municipality building in Sharjah, including H.E. Ahmed Bin Sulayem (far left), Mahdi Al Tajir (next to Sulayem), Mokhtar Al Toum (with arms crossed)., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref32_000024_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 14 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Clocks/Watches; Facial Hair; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Buildings
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr performing the Al Ayala dance with a crowd of men behind him., Circa 1965-1969; AD_MC_093_ref32_000025_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 14 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Crowds; Gatherings; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Dancing; Swords/Knives; Weapons; United Arab Emirates; Percussion Instruments; Musical Instruments
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle) at a dinner for a delegation., Circa 1969-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000026_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 14 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Food; Gatherings; Officials; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Drinks/Beverages; United Arab Emirates
  - A portrait of a man smoking a cigarette., Circa 1960-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000027_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 14 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Cigarettes; Smoking; Unknown Locations; Furnishings
  - A group portrait of officials congregating at the municipality building in Sharjah, including H.E. Ahmed Bin Sulayem (far left), Mahdi Al Tajir (next to Sulayem), Mokhtar Al Toum (second from the right)., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref32_000028_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 13.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Officials; Buildings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Clocks/Watches; Head Covers/Veils
  - From the left: H.E. Saeed Al Darmaki, an unidentified man, H.H. Sheikh Ahmad Bin Ali Al Thani, H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.H. Sheikh Mohammed Bin Khalid Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, H.H. Sheikh Mubarak Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan on a tour., Circa 1968-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000029_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 7.4 x 10.6 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Group Portraits; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Crowds; Buildings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - An unidentified man (left) smoking with Mohammed Badr (right)., Circa 1960-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000030_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 14 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Cigarettes; Smoking; Unknown Locations; Cameras; Clocks/Watches
  - A group portrait of students from the United Arab Emirates in Cairo., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref32_000031_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Students; Cairo, Egypt; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Art; Facial Hair; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - A portrait of H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (right) with an unidentified man (left) on a plane., Circa 1968-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000032_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Airplanes; Transportation; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Unknown Locations; Men; Individual Portraits; Presidents; Royalty; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - A view of abras in the Dubai Creek., Circa 1950-1955; AD_MC_093_ref32_000033_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 6.1 x 6.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Water; Rivers; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Buildings; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Men; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress
  - From the left: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, H.H. Sheikh Rashid Bin Saeed Al Maktoum, H.H. Sheikh Khalifa Bin Hamad Al Thani, and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan., Circa 1969; AD_MC_093_ref32_000034_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 21.7 x 16.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Men; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Royalty; Officials; Gatherings; Political Leadership; Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1912-1990; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - A portrait of H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi in H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's office., Circa 1968-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000035_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 21.5 x 16.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Offices; United Arab Emirates; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - The back cover of an album of assorted images of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1950-1970; AD_MC_093_ref32_000036_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.7 x 25.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; United Arab Emirates; Paris, France; Unknown Locations; Cairo, Egypt
- Continental Circus in Dubai 24 May 1972
  - The front cover of the album "Continental Circus in Dubai 24 May 1972.", May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000001_000001; Studio Photo Flash, Dubai, United Arab Emirates; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - The inside front cover of the album "Continental Circus in Dubai 24 May 1972.", May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000002_000001; Studio Photo Flash, Dubai, United Arab Emirates; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; English Writing
  - From the top down: a view of the Continental Circus tent; a group of men at the Continental Circus, including H.H. Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (fourth from the left); and performers at the Continental Circus., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000003_000001; Studio Photo Flash, Dubai, United Arab Emirates; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Tents; Gatherings; Performing Arts; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Electricity; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Royalty; Women; Flags; Costumes; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Officials; Events/Occasions; Political Leadership; Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1949-
  - Three views of H.H. Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (middle, with walking stick) entering the Continental Circus with a group of men., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000004_000001; Studio Photo Flash, Dubai, United Arab Emirates; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Group Portraits; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Royalty; Officials; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Hats; Military/Soldiers; Gatherings; Canes/Walking Sticks; Boys; Children; Clocks/Watches; Events/Occasions; Political Leadership; Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1949-
  - Top: H.H. Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum cutting a ribbon at the opening ceremony of the Continental Circus. Bottom: H.H. Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum speaking to a group of people at the opening ceremony of the Continental Circus., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000005_000001; Studio Photo Flash, Dubai, United Arab Emirates; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Performing Arts; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Ceremonies; Gatherings; Men; Group Portraits; Royalty; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Girls; Children; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Audiences/Spectators; Events/Occasions; Political Leadership; Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1949-
  - Top: performers at the Continental Circus. Bottom: H.H. Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (middle) with a group of men watching the Continental Circus., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000006_000001; Studio Photo Flash, Dubai, United Arab Emirates; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Performing Arts; Tents; Gatherings; Costumes; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Royalty; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Boys; Children; Audiences/Spectators; Clocks/Watches; Events/Occasions; Political Leadership; Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1949-
  - Top: performers at the Continental Circus. Bottom: H.H. Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (second from the right) with a group of men watching the Continental Circus., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000007_000001; Studio Photo Flash, Dubai, United Arab Emirates; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Group Portraits; Women; Individual Portraits; Costumes; Tents; Performing Arts; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Audiences/Spectators; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Royalty; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Children; Boys; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Events/Occasions; Political Leadership; Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1949-
  - Two views of performers at the Continental Circus in Dubai., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000008_000001; Studio Photo Flash, Dubai, United Arab Emirates; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Women; Men; Group Portraits; Individual Portraits; Performing Arts; Audiences/Spectators; Costumes; Tents; Events/Occasions
  - Two views of performers at the Continental Circus in Dubai., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000009_000001; Studio Photo Flash, Dubai, United Arab Emirates; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Performing Arts; Costumes; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Events/Occasions; Audiences/Spectators; Tents
  - Two views of performers at the Continental Circus in Dubai., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000010_000001; Studio Photo Flash, Dubai, United Arab Emirates; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Costumes; Performing Arts; Individual Portraits; Group Portraits; Tents; Events/Occasions; Women; Men; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Furnishings
  - Two views of performers at the Continental Circus in Dubai., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000011_000001; Studio Photo Flash, Dubai, United Arab Emirates; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Performing Arts; Costumes; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Umbrellas/Parasols; Women; Men; Events/Occasions; Tents; Audiences/Spectators
  - Two views of performers at the Continental Circus in Dubai., May 24 1972; AD_MC_093_ref33_000012_000001; Studio Photo Flash, Dubai, United Arab Emirates; 1 Photographic Prints 28.7 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Performing Arts; Men; Women; Costumes; Group Portraits; Tents; Events/Occasions; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Audiences/Spectators